# Mohammad Javad Majlesi

# Front-End Developer (Reactjs)

Isfahan, Tehran , Iran Male , Single , 2005-05-22

(+98) 9134389783 (+98) 9922905410 mohammadjavadmajlesi313@gmail.com

#### **About me**

I am Highly motivated front-end developer with a strong desire to learn and grow. With 1 year of expertise in building websites and projects.

I think the most important thing about me is that I am a fast learner.

I think the most important thing about me is that I am a fast learner and flexible, which makes me fit well with any team.

\* Also, in my current situation, I am more interested in learning and gaining more experience, and the requested salary is not important to me

#### **SKILLS**

React js , TypeScript , TailwindCss , Bootstrap , JavaScript , Html , Css React Hooks , React Query , React Context , Git , Material-UI Web , Restful api , Sass

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Atrin-fanavaran Company, Isfahan** - React-Developer

June 2024 - August 2024 (3 month)

I spent three months as an intern in this company and was able to do various projects with React

Tools used: React, TypeScript, React Hooks, React Query, ....

#### **Quera Company, Tehran** - Front-end Developer

March 2024 - May 2024 (4 month)

In this self-taught online course, I learned the basics of front-end, namely HTML, CSS, Js , Tailwind, etc. and did various projects.

Tools used: Html, Css, JavaScript, Tailwind, Restful api, ....

#### **EDUCATION**

## Hamedan University of Technology , Hamedan

September 2023 - present

3rd semester of computer software engineering.

#### **AWARDS**

#### Quera

- https://quera.org/certificate/ATbRv9JX/

## **Linkedin and Github**

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohammad-javad-majlesi-0ab27331a/
- <a href="https://github.com/mjmajlesi">https://github.com/mjmajlesi</a>

# Languages

English

Level - Intermediate